<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Ivan Notes</title>
  <subtitle>A feed of the latest notes about what we I&#39;m doing or feeling writing about.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://www.ivanfrantar.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://www.ivanfrantar.com/" />
  <updated>2024-07-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://www.ivanfrantar.com</id>
  <author>
    <name>Ivan Frantar</name>
    <email>ivan@ivanfrantar.com</email>
  </author>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>First post after site redesign</title>
    <link href="https://www.ivanfrantar.com/notes/first-post-after-site-redesign/" />
    <updated>2024-07-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://www.ivanfrantar.com/notes/first-post-after-site-redesign/</id>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[
        <p>Hello everyone,</p>
<p>I’m excited to announce the first redesign of my website in a while! This update marks a fresh start not just for the site’s look and feel, but also for how I engage a number of topics or interests I might like to write about.</p>
<p>In the past, I haven’t been very active in writing, often finding myself sharing snippets, reposts, and replies on platforms like X.com and other social networks. However, I’ve decided to be more proactive from the realm of my own website. Moving forward, I’m committing to writing more thoughtful and periodic posts here on my blog. This space will serve as a journal where I can explore and share the things I’m passionate about.</p>
<h3>A few interests I'm into:</h3>
<p><strong>Design and Product Design</strong>: Obviously, as a designer, I’m constantly fascinated by the evolving landscape of design. I’ll be sharing insights, adding more case studies, and my thoughts on the everything related design and product design and development.</p>
<p><strong>Fitness</strong>: I've been doing resistance training for over a year (I know is not that impressive so far), and has become an important aspect of my life. Being a father of two girls, I am committed to staying as fit as possible, not only to be there for them as they grow, but also to ensure that anyone who dares to mess with them thinks twice 😉. So, Expect posts about some workouts, including some PR videos deadlifting, bench pressing, and squats or anything related.</p>
<p><strong>Nutrition</strong>: I have learned (or rather I'm learning) how important nutrition is for your fitness goals and your overall health. This area of what I might post could be boring for some given that I focus in macronutrients for small range of foods. However it can be exciting if you like steaks and eggs as much as I do which is 80% of my diet. I might post thousand photos of steaks from slightly different angles. You've been warned (of deliciousness)! Anyway is all about learning.</p>
<p><strong>Bitcoin and the Concept of Money</strong>: Recently, I’ve started learning about Bitcoin and its broader implications on the concept of money. I'm fascinated by its nature as a protocol operating on a decentralized network using blockchain technology detached from governments, central banks or any country's economy or policy decisions. I look forward to exploring how Bitcoin is reshaping our understanding of money, value, and financial systems.</p>
<p>I don’t know exactly where this journey will lead, but that’s part of the excitement. This blog will be a space for me to explore these interests and any new ones that come along. Think of it as a collection of my thoughts and ideas – what I like to call “thought farts.”</p>
<p>If any of these topics are of interest to anybody, or if anyone enjoy reading about random musings, I invite you to follow along. Feel free to get in touch with any feedback or comments you may have. Anyone's insights will be invaluable as I kick start this new journey.</p>
<p>As for this website, under the hood I'm using <a href="https://netlify.com">Netlify</a> and I have decided to use <a href="https://11ty.dev">11ty.dev</a> as the scaffolding to make it work. Both of this platforms are amazing and easy to learn (and I'm still learning the ins and outs). I'll be changing and updating the website design along the journey; the temptation of having this space to do whatever I want is too much.</p>
<p>Thanks for joining me. Stay tuned for more updates, and I look forward to sharing my thoughts and experiences with you all.</p>

      ]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>